<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<!-- Logo is a direct link to a jpg /png file. This logo will be used if an individual mod does not have one. -->
	<!-- If logo is not specified, the mod launcher's default will be shown. -->
	<ServerGroup Name="7DVR" Logo="https://staticdelivery.nexusmods.com/mods/1059/images/3011/3011-1687150704-107959013.png" Description="7D2D VR Overhaul!">
		<!-- Logo is a direct link to a jpg /png file. Default image dimension is 2064x452 -->
		<Server Name="7DVR" Logo="https://staticdelivery.nexusmods.com/mods/1059/images/3011/3011-1687150704-107959013.png">
			<Description>Experience the world of 7 Days to Die in Virtual Reality!
Supports full motion controls and 6DOF.

Have you ever wanted to truly feel like you were surviving in a zombie apocalypse? 
Do you long to huddle in a dirty basement by torchlight while something makes horrible noises and bangs on the door above?
This might be the mod for you. 

It has 6DOF tracking
It has motion controls
It has physical melee combat (or you can use triggers--you do you!)
It has in game settings menu (options->controls->VR)
It has first person vehicle controls (and child lock seat belts for the gyrocopter if desired)
It has the ability to customize your grip/hold on any item saved to your copy of the game
It has smooth turn, snap turn, roomscale turn
It has the ability to move in the direction of your headset or the direction of your controller
It has the ability to dance and watch your arms, legs, or shadow mirror your actions!!!
It has the ability to see your other friend in VR wave to you. (Even if you are a flat player using this mod)
It has bugs you have never seen or ever thought possible in 7D2D!!!
It does NOT have 2 handed bows or real working scopes YET (On the TODO List).
It does NOT have a ton of other features we still want to add!  Look for updates in the future!

Supports play between flat screen players and VR. 
Client side only for mod install... no server alterations required (NO EAC though)

Compatible with MANY other mods including overhauls like Darkness Falls, District Zero, etc.
				
For more up to date information and discussion please join the 7D discord
https://flat2vr.com/ 

</Description>
			
			
			<!-- Who made -->
			<Author>Kaaliba and Necro</Author>
			
			<!-- 
				This forces the mod launcher to make a copy of the game for the mod. 
				Mod that use BepInEx, and relative paths should use this setting.
				Remove Deploy or change it to Partial to skip that step
			-->
			<Deploy>Full</Deploy>
			
			<!-- This is the alpha version you last tested with -->
			<!-- You can use Latest if you just want the current one -->
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			
			<!-- Have a discord you want people to join? -->
			<Discord>http://flat2vr.com/</Discord>
			<!-- Got a website -->
	        <WebSite></WebSite>
			
			<!-- Twitter? -->
            <Twitter></Twitter>
			
			<!-- Want to give people an option to donate? -->
            <Donate>https://www.patreon.com/7DaysVR</Donate>		

			<!-- Got some release notes you want people to view? -->
			<ReleaseNotes>https://www.nexusmods.com/7daystodie/mods/3011?tab=description</ReleaseNotes>
			
			<!-- Only the first download is used -->
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/7DVR/7DVR_Release</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>
